who is BT Kingsley like who is the man
of BT Kingsley BT Kingsley is uh a
confident humble original individual
original individual original like I just
be doing stuff like I I have all my
random phases is to do colors up like a
colge shirt and I had words on the back
like yeah you I see you looking like
that you want want to try something if
you want yeah like there was a scarf
phase there was two watches but anybody
two watches two watches just on the same
East Coast West Coast that's how I was I
was let me make sure this is say on TV I
was the first comedian to wear lights on
his shoes on stage the first Gary Owens
I saw you Nick Cannon I saw you lights I
was first listen I love four years ago I
love that that's what pissed him
off give me no credit I love to that's
what piss these mother steing the lights
on the
shoes lights on the shoes two watches so
you're a trend Setter a trend Setter
Trend Setter in my head at least that's
not in your head that's what you are
that's what you're doing okay talk to me
about this right here uh grown and sexy
this is uh a Comedy Night with grown
serious I've seen uh very many of these
on the ground on the very listen hey you
guys when y'all take the flight just say
I rather you say no then throw throw it
in the trash throw it in your purse
throw it in the back of your car don't
throw it on the ground after you done
looked me in the face said you was
coming you know what I'm going to be I
ain't got nothing to
do I a got nothing to do fast forward to
10 seconds later and it's everywhere you
ever you ever pick one up and Chase the
person down absolutely I just saw you
dropped the
phone Mama you know you better than
this